we are on our own land, this is on the territory of
мы на своей земле это на территории
ukraine and you are occupiers of
украины а вы оккупанты
91 since 91
91 года с 91 года
when the state was created independent
когда создалась государстве независимые
ukraine looks like this wait you
такая кроится выглядит подождите вы вы
now you are now a citizen of which fillet and
сейчас вы сейчас гражданин какой филе и
country you all have a passport of the
страны все у вас есть паспорт вот
russian federation when let's
российской федерации когда допустим
say
допустим
well look you  You may not agree
ну смотрите вы вы можете не согласиться
that Moscow is now not part of the
что москва сейчас не является частью там
Tatar-Mongolian horde
татаро-монгольского орды
there. They were destroyed that they lived with smoothies. Look, they stole me.
смотрите меня украли мы сделали какие
repay here why did you change the
погасите сюда а почему вы поменяли
passport of the Soviet Union to the passport of the
паспорт советского союза на паспорт
Russian Federation left.
российской федерации осталось . меня
no one asked me to
никто не спрашивал
flog you now, but in a quiet way, you quietly
вы сейчас высечь а по тихой вы по тихой
voted your Ukraine there and went out
проголосовали там свои украиной и вышли
in a quiet way, yes,
по тихой нормально да и
and when the Russian Federation was created and
а когда создалась российская федерация а
what date and month the
какого числа и месяца
army the whole country and the entire Soviet
воинство вся страна и весь советский
Union voted for the preservation of the
союз проголосовал за сохранение
Soviet Union of the computer in the region of 75
советского союза компьютера в районе 75
and 76 percent was right there in a couple of
и 76 процентов было тут же через пару
months ukraine stirs up its referendum
месяцев украина мутит свой референдум
vote that we are separating
голосуй что мы отделяемся
tell me when ukraine became part of the
скажите а когда украина стала частью
soviet union
советского союза
when i ask you only them
когда вот я вас прошу лишь них
ever never when ukraine became part of the
когда-никогда когда украина стала частью
soviet union
советского союза
in the form in which it is now to me
в таком виде в котором она сейчас мне
at all  here was the
вообще вот было украинской народной
city of the Ukrainian People's Republic, look and what I
республике сити смотри и что она я себя
imagined myself as a
представляло
fish that represented the Kuban still
рыба что представлял кубань еще
represented there a lot of territories you will
представляла там очень много территорий
attach yes,
пристроишь да
you just know what to do I
просто вы знаете какой то делать я
look at all Russians to this imperial
смотрю у всех русских к это имперское
thinking here you are in which region of Russia you
мышление вот вы в каком регионе россии
live close here Siberia  here you live
живете близко тут сибирь вот вы живете
somewhere far away in siberia this is
где-то далеко в сибирь это
ukraine you don’t wear here you live where  it’s
украина не носите вот вы живете где-то
far away in Siberia, so here I am, born in the
далеко в сибири так и вот я рожденный в
USSR
ссср
, they stole native Russian lands from me there,
у меня украли там исконно русские земли
so it turns out,
так получается а
but when I don’t have any corners, but you
вот когда пусть у меня нет уголкам а вы
wait, we don’t have to
подождите у нас нет
wait, wait again, we are
подождите подождите еще раз у нас
going to buy Russia, so now
проходит покупаться россии так сейчас
Ukraine
украина
Ukraine was  make up even if you
украина была составить даже если
look at the Soviet Union so a
смотреть в составе советского союза так
separate republic russia was also a
отдельная республику россия была также
separate republic so
отдельные республика так
ukraine by the way was a subject
украина кстати было субъектом
co-founder organizations of ideal
сооснователем организациями идеальных
nations true
наций правда
it was
было
b s r s r r the ussr were one of the pine
б с с р с с р р ссср были одними сосна
countries the founder did it just turn out
стран основатель ли он только получается
that we were a subject yes  and
что мы были субъектом да и вот вас
now it’s bombing you that you live in Siberia and
сейчас бомбит что вы живете в сибири и
so, but there is a whale, the primordially Russian lands
так но там кита исконно русские земли
that were once somewhere on old
которые когда-то где-то были на давних
maps do not now belong to your
картах так не принадлежат сейчас вашей
empire
империи
in
в
favor of yes, a little more, yes, but still
пользу да уже чуть больше да а еще
good, and a little more there  neither were these
хорошо а еще чуть больше там ни были эти
territories like that, but a little more they
территории так а еще чуть больше снова
were again and again weren’t so on, though,
были и снова не были так дальше правда
only Ukraine is good, let’s do it, oh, and
только украины хорошо давайте так ой а
Siberia, let’s  r siberia so
сибирь давайте с каких пор сибирь так
belongs there to the russian empire does it belong to the
принадлежит там российской империи ли
tsardom of moscow
там московскому царству каких
what kind of like what year
вот как как каком году
17 i.e. it turns out if we dig the
17 то есть получается если мы копнем
maps even deeper then someone there saying
карты еще глубже тогда кто-то там сказав
camp or whale the mongols will say wait
стана или кита монголы скажут подожди
it was once the possession of genghis khan and
это когда-то была владение чингисхан и
why
почему
some-  then the tribes go
какие-то племена выезжай воевали
out fought cut out before you get out they didn’t get out but
вырезали до получаете от не вылезали но
like this I’m in a small town from the
таким вот я в маленького городка с
lower children’s city please
города нижнюю детского пожалуйста
put how much you
ставьте по сколько вас насколько вас
wear these on turn on let me say this
носить эти на включаете дайте это говорю
one of the smallest probably in
одно из самых маленьких наверное по
terms of the number of peoples of Russia
численности народов россии
how many do you have in your town  population,
сколько у вас в вашем городке население
I just look
я просто смотришь
better already, yes, because I hear than people
уже лучше да потому что я слышу чем люди
from a smaller town somewhere there to go
с меньшей городка где-то там себе идти
men the theme of a larger imperial nickname is pulled together
men тему ник большей имперской стягивают
and you know they have the feeling that they
и знать вот они такое ощущение что они
are somehow not like they are not like they somehow
какие-то не такие они не как они как-то
compensate here  this is their own, then
компенсируют вот это свою затем они у
they hang the gates of Europe and the USA, probably
них завис калиток европе и сша наверное
yes, you also said something about America in this
да вот вы в этом про америку тоже
and it turns out that you
говорили что-то и получается что вы
want this is what you  m everything is
хотите вот чем вам все
sharper than Siberia will be for you, for example, it
острее чем вам сибири будет например на
removes your
удаляет ваша
subservience, how do you know
подобострастия какое-то вот как знаете
how you can lag under them
вы как лагов под на них можно вот там
?
вы вот вы я хотел тот же спросить кстати
there was no prefix and
вы были в европе нет ни было приставки и
even desire, and for some reason, all
даже желания и какого почему-то вот все
Russians, not almost all say, I have not been to
русские не почти все говорят я не был в
Europe and don’t even want to go there, but why should I
европе и даже не хочу туда а зачем мне
go there, maybe you
туда а может быть вы до сих пор можете
can still see how the
бы посмотрели как вот там европейской
bailiff of European civilization is there  Can you imagine
цивилизации пристав вы представляете что
what Russia is in general I wanted to imagine,
такое россия в общем хотела представляю
but this is what these dimensions are, these time
но это такое эти размеры эти часовые
zones are large, different climatic zones are
пояса велики разные климатические зоны
different one by one the very village of
разные по одной то самое селение
Russian Russian citizens
российским российские граждане
Russian citizens are the same,
российские граждане как одни и те же вот
look, let’s say between Nizhneudinsk there
смотрите допустим между нижнеудинске там
are mostly Russian Ukrainians for a minute
в основном русские украины минуту
citizens of Russia then  there is a post from school but
граждане россии то есть пост со школы же
no yes yes yes yes yes, that is, the basis of the
нет да да да да да то есть основу
Slavic appearance having moved to Irkutsk,
славянская внешность переехав в иркутск
there are a lot of Buryats here, for example,
здесь очень много бурятов допустим
because  it’s not far to
потому что здесь недалеко
walk and the land there they grow a course and
гулять и земли там они выращивают ход и
a lot of people of [ __ ] heat,
очень много людей монголоидной тепла
that is, everything is different, you understand, I’ll go
то есть все по-разному понимаете я поеду
let’s say Tatarstan there people like Paris
допустим татарстан там люди будто париже
I ate it all former Soviet
я поедал это все бывшие советские
citizens former former words difference I
граждане бывший бывший слова разница я
understand that this is the country you want to do
понимаю что вот страна вы хотите сделать
I  no, I’m not talking about nations, I’m not three
я нет я не про нации я сейчас не три
nations now, selling here, you get it,
нации продажа вот выпал вы получается
apart from the heritage of the Soviet Union, you
кроме наследия советского союза больше
haven’t seen anything anywhere else in the world, so it
нигде в мире ничего не видели так
turns out, what should I see in the world
получается а что я должен увидеть в мире
that I don’t have,
чего у меня нет
well, how to become very good
ну вот хорош как стать очень хорошего
about that, you can  to know and to come to
про то вы можете знать и вот приехать
see there the same tree the same
увидеть там такой же дерево такой же
comment kush droshky so but you can see
коммент куш дрожку так но можете увидеть
some completely different relationship
какой то совсем другое взаимоотношения
among people so you can see some
среди людей так можете увидеть какое-то
other social structure so you can
другое социальное устройство так можете
see some processes there
увидеть какие-то процессы там
democratic and maybe vice versa
демократическим и может наоборот
totalitarian
тоталитарной не
you can’t  somehow you will begin to understand the
может вы как-то начнете больше понимать
world more like this, and for example, your views are already there,
мир так и например и ваши уже
for example, here we once had somewhere on the
воззрение например вот у нас где то на
map  this is the area we
карте было когда-то вот это области нам
need to take it away, maybe they were gone,
надо ее забрать может они были пропали
listen, let’s say I’m 40 years old, and I
слушайте вот мне допустим 40 лет да и я
have no illusions about Europe
иллюзии никаких у питаю по поводу европы
from Europe,
с европы к нам нашу на нашу страну
two of the most destructive wars
приходила две самые разрушительные войны
in all of the history of mankind came to us in our country,
за все за всю историю человечества
do you think that we  we forgot the whole
вы думаете что мы тут забыли все это
thing here, we didn’t forget them, and even living in
дело них мы не забыли и даже живя в
Siberia people still remember, although they
сибири люди до сих пор помнят хотя они
didn’t trample on their boots here, but everyone
здесь сапогами сами не топтали но у всех
somehow died in this war,
так или иначе люди умирали на этой войне
relatives of grandfathers and great-grandfathers, let’s
родственники деды и прадеды у меня
say my grandfather did not participate in the Russian line of
допустим дед не участвовал русской линии
war  it was with the fascists with the Germans that the
войне именно с фашистами с немцами а
Japanese participated in the war from the Japanese
участвовал японцами войны с японской
war in the Japanese theater of
войны на японском театре военных
operations,
действий
I understand that no matter how fashionable it is
я понимаю что у вас как бы это не модно
there on May 9, well, why would we and I on
там 9 мая ну как бы зачем нам и мне 8
May 8, according to the flesh, together with Europe, that we
мая по плоти вместе с европой то что мы
lost this war  we rejoice in the pool,
проиграли эту войну омут радуемся я
I came right, I’m just new joys,
приехал я правом я просто новые радости
I just think that the modern world is
я просто считаю что современный мир он
so open and so you know,
настолько открыты и так и вот знаете
before we could live in one country, then in a
раньше мы могли жить в одной стране то в
year we lived in the council already in  the seventy-
год мы жили в совет уже восемьдесят
first year of birth, how did you understand it so
первого года рождения какие вы так это
40 years old and told me too 40 me
понимала 40 лет и сказали мне тоже 40 я
too and how many 9 years I lived in the USSR
тоже и сколько 9 лет еще пожил в ссср
here here and it turns out that then we
здесь здесь и получается что тогда у нас
had an iron curtain so they
был железный занавес так ездить на
didn’t let them go anywhere on purpose now
специально не выпускали никуда теперь у
we have the opportunity
нас есть возможность
and  here people in ukraine go to europe
и вот люди в украине ездят в европу
see how people live so there
видят как люди живут так есть этом туда
is some kind of cultural exchange going there, then
идет какой-то культурный обмен то
life is cut short, it's a
жизнь оборвалась
pity we can cut it off here and
жалко можем может здесь на оборвалась и
even often it starts like a true story,
даже часто так начинается трушке былью
we read this is someone with 6 shorter
читаем это кто-то с 6 короче сразу
standing immediately and also exquisite  with a sound in
стоять а также изысканные звуком в
Ludovik,
людовик
here is a character of hearts, such a
вот червовый персонаж у такого решения
decision was sucked out on some give in the hands of 50
там высосали на некий дать в руки 50
pancakes to garbage blood and century mini take that
блины мусору кровь и век мини take that
when i 70 by widely popular twin in
when i 70 по широко народження twin в
that USSR by 6 rocket in peace in a
том ссср по 6 rocket in peace тоном
small tone guf there is a shaitan belt and once an Arab for
малым guf там шайтан пояс и раз араба
hours  ice creams and behave the king of his
часам пломбиров и behave царь своего
village so 300 and 1000 one of the
поселку так 300 и 1000 кто-то из чем
fewer of these and forbid their places pt
меньше вот таких и запретишь их места пт
they would not starve the empire to him for what he needs
им бы не морить империи ему для чего ему
Europe to ours or Europe is shorter
то европы до нашему не то европа короче
I’m here, there, Siberia’s way, but here’s a
я вот тут себе там сибири путь но вот
little
чуть
primordially Russian land, the cyst, the mother
исконно русские земли киста материнскую
region, he’s there, Kharkiv wines, he wants to see a
область ему там харькове вин хоче виде
waste for a black dude, Toby, let’s say that the
трата для черный чувак тоби скажем то
Podolsk region is still a vacation here,
подольского область еще каникулы сюда
water, a vain drive, the headquarters, you’re not hungry in the
вода суетный езды штаб ты не голоден в
union, the bushes are upset by Tambov,
унию кустам огорчена тамбов string
you see the one for  tbc tacos and
видишь ту для tbc тако и
nothing.  retinue you live in your
ничего . свиту ты живешь в свои там
lightning bolts of siberia in the village itself it
молнии сибири в самом поселке это
moved to the regional center happy with
перебрался в областной центр довольным
that
же того
kid came to success and
пацан к успеху пришел и
you are peter and suffer to know and suit a
ты петр и мучиться знать и костюм
snack tile there they already took refuge to find
закуску плитку там уж укрылись найти
at least there maps of medieval so that
хоть там картах средневековых так что
istanbul and south mexico so much finya
стамбул и south мехико столько финя
nation  infected by the imperial who with such a
нация заражена имперскими кем с таким
virus, they will propagate all i was the
вирусом им пропаганду all i was the
hands and so the grass will drop out the floor
рукам и так и трава будут выбывать этаж
for one kind of misha will open up I will demand
на один вид миша раскроюсь я потребую
demilitarization and put on kittens
демилитаризации и да нацепи котята
someone socially from the slave itself,
кто-то социально самой от раба буда
writing to the collapse of Russia in Ukraine, the state is
писля распаду россии на украине державы
like a Bavarian father  I wouldn’t
так отца баварского будто я бы не
laugh at the
смеялась
life of clowns, so you, with an Internet
жизни клоуны так и вы с интернет
emphasis on a disco, sir service throughout the
акцентом на дискотеке сэр сервис по всей
Russian Federation,
российской федерации штучные
Mayra’s piece political creations, escape on the
политического творения майра спастись на
rubber of the state and
резине державы и
us deer, then the boiled laptop of the powers of May
нас оленя то ноут вареный держав мая
passes, and the batchat is such,
проходит а батчата такую
let’s say, the first bumpkin to a couple of initials, and
скажем первых увальня паре навчальний а
so they need to explain  us cliques usta
так им потребно пояснять нас клики устя
propaganda the ruins of the shaft they are not the bridge socks
пропаганда руины вала их не мост носки
he propaganda and hp cheated on discounts
he пропагандой и хп обманывала на скидки
here in  I replaced the kitty title in
вот вин заместила чтобы титула кисы в
that it’s a litmus and I take
том это лакмус и беру
one of my cotton wool to live as well as an hour
одну ваты свои жить а также часовую
to the governor there to say
региону губернатору там там сказать о
what about this mass of krush so black
чего вот об этом массу крюша так черного
asphalt suitcase I’m leaving to
асфальта чемодан ухожу
kill what is there grass saw pad
умертвить то что там трава saw pad
Ukrainian lands
украинские земли